export const questionAndAnswers = [
    {
        "question": "When a plant needs more than 50% humidity, what kind of plant is it?",
        "answer": "Tropical",
    },
    {
        "question": "What can you do for plants to improve their ability to photosynthesize?",
        "answer": "Dust or clean off the leaves",
    },
    {
        "question": "When a plant develops pests, what is the first thing you should do?",
        "answer": "Isolate the plant from other plants",
    },
    {
        "question": "Question about plants",
        "answer": "Answer about plants",
    },
    {
        "question": "What plant is known for looking perked up at night but droopy by day?",
        "answer": "Prayer Plant or Maranta",
    },
    {
        "question": "If a plant starts to develop yellow spots in the middle of its leaves, what could be the culprit?",
        "answer": "Overwatering or Fungus infection",
    },
    {
        "question": "When a plant needs more than 50% humidity, what kind of plant is it?",
        "answer": "Tropical",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is it called when plants develop holes or slits in the leaves as they receive more sunlight?",
        "answer": "Fenestration",
    },
    {
        "question": "What indoor plant is the best for purifying air, as tested by NASA?",
        "answer": "English Ivy",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is an unlikely booster for plant growth?",
        "answer": "Music",
    },
]